<?xml-model href="https://tei-c.org/release/xml/tei/custom/schema/relaxng/tei_lite.rng"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="https://go.KIBI.family/Tools/XSLT/KiT2X.xslt"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" href='data:text/css,
*.tei.text *.tei.front,*.tei.text *.tei.body{ Padding-Inline: 0; Font-Variant-Numeric: Proportional-Nums Lining-Nums; Text-Align: Start; Hyphens: None }
*.tei.text *.tei.head{ Margin-Block: 0 }
*.tei.text *.tei.front>div>*.tei.div>div>*.tei.head{ Font: Inherit; Text-Decoration: Underline }
*.tei.text *.tei.front>div>*.tei.div>div{ Display: Grid; Grid-Template-Columns: 60% 40% }
*.tei.text *.tei.front>div>*.tei.div>div>*{ Grid-Column: 1 / Span 2 }
*.tei.text *.tei.front>div>*.tei.div>div *.tei.closer{ Grid-Column: 2 / Span 1; Text-Align: Start }
*.tei.text *.tei.front *.tei.signed{ Text-Align: Start }
*.tei.text *.tei.figure.warn{ Display: Grid; Margin: Auto; Border: Thin Solid; Grid-Template-Rows: Repeat(3, Auto); Grid-Template-Columns: Subgrid }
*.tei.text *.tei.figure.warn>figcaption{ Grid-Row: 1 / Span 1; Grid-Column: 1 / Span 3; Margin: 0; Font-Variant-Caps: Inherit; Text-Transform: Uppercase }
*.tei.text *.tei.figure.warn>figcaption>*.tei.head{ Margin: 0; Border-Block-Start: None; Border-Block-End: Thin Solid; Padding: 0; Font-Size: 3EM; Text-Align: Start }
*.tei.text *.tei.figure.warn>*.tei.p{ Grid-Row: 2 / Span 1; Grid-Column: 1 / Span 3; Text-Indent: 0 }
*.tei.text *.tei.figure.warn *.tei.graphic{ Display: Block; Float: Inline-Start; Margin-Block: 0; Margin-Inline: 0 .25EM; Border-Block-End: Thin Solid; Border-Inline-End: Thin Solid; Max-Block-Size: None }
*.tei.text *.tei.figure.warn>*.tei.closer{ Display: Grid; Block-Size: Max-Content; Grid-Template-Rows: Auto Auto; Grid-Template-Columns: Max-Content Max-Content; Align-Items: End; Font-Size: Smaller }
*.tei.text *.tei.figure.warn *.tei.signed{ Display: Contents; Font-Size: Larger; Text-Align: Start }
*.tei.text *.tei.figure.warn *.tei.signed::after{ Display: Block; Grid-Row: 2 / Span 1; Grid-Column: 1 / Span 1; Content: "" }
*.tei.text *.tei.body *.tei.head{ Margin-Inline: 3EM; Font: Normal 2EM Monospace; Text-Align: Start }
*.tei.text *.tei.p{ Text-Align: Start; Text-Indent: 1.5EM }
*.tei.text *.tei.opener,*.tei.text *.tei.closer{ Margin: 0 }
*.tei.text *.tei.postscript *.tei.label{ Font: Inherit }
*.tei.text *.tei.postscript *.tei.label+*.tei.p{ Text-Indent: 0 }
*.tei.text *.tei.q::before{ Content: "“" }
*.tei.text *.tei.q::after{ Content: "”" }
*.tei.text *.tei.q+*.tei.seg.space{ Display: Inline }
*.tei.text *.tei.abbr{ Font-Variant-Caps: Inherit }
*.tei.text *.tei.emph{ Text-Decoration: Underline }
*.tei.text *.tei.strong{ Font-Weight: Bolder }
*.tei.text *.tei.soCalled.oblique{ Font-Weight: Bolder; Font-Style: Oblique }
*.tei.text *.tei.emph::before,*.tei.text *.tei.emph::after,*.tei.text *.tei.soCalled.oblique::before,*.tei.text *.tei.soCalled.oblique::after{ Content: None }
*.tei.text *.tei.seg.cursiveonline{ Font-Family: Cursive; Border-Block-End: Thin Solid }
*.tei.text *.tei.seg.cursiveonline::before,*.tei.text *.tei.seg.cursiveonline::after{ Content: " " }
'?>
<TEI xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0" xml:lang="en">
	<teiHeader>
		<fileDesc>
			<titleStmt>
				<title level="m">In the Palm of My Hand</title>
				<author><name>BJMNS</name><note>As Tyler Fengat.</note></author>
			</titleStmt>
			<editionStmt>
				<edition><idno type="URI">tag:bjmns.tumblr.com,2013:bns::3:1:0:1</idno></edition>
			</editionStmt>
			<publicationStmt>
				<publisher>KIBI Gô</publisher>
				<date when="2020">2020</date>
				<availability status="free">
					<licence target="https://creativecommons.org/publicdomain/zero/1.0/"><title level="m">CC0 1.0 Universal Public Domain Dedication</title></licence>
				</availability>
				<ptr target="https://go.KIBI.family/Corpora/BJMNS/3/1/0/1/text.xml"/>
			</publicationStmt>
			<sourceDesc>
				<p>Source is a handwritten draft (pencil on college‐ruled notebook paper).</p>
			</sourceDesc>
		</fileDesc>
		<encodingDesc>
			<editorialDecl>
				<p>Quotes are marked up using TEI; no attempt to mark up names or titles of works has been made, as they received no special treatment in the source.</p>
				<p>Mistakes are preserved as written. Additions are noted with the <gi>add</gi> element and strikeouts with <gi>del</gi>.</p>
				<p>The page with the author’s note has a header consisting of <q type="written" xml:space="preserve">B@N	In the Palm of My Hand</q> and a B@N logotype in the corner (reproduced: <graphic url="./B@N.png" height="185px" width="157px" scale=".48"><desc>B@N logotype.</desc></graphic>); this is not transcribed.</p>
			</editorialDecl>
		</encodingDesc>
		<revisionDesc status="published">
			<change when="2020-08-04" status="published">Revised to reflect original handwritten source, including the addition of the author’s note. <gi>editionStmt</gi> and <gi>revisionDesc</gi> added.</change>
			<change when="2020-07-31" status="published">Initial version based of a Rich Text Format transcription.</change>
		</revisionDesc>
	</teiHeader>
	<text>
		<front>
			<div>
				<head>Author’s Note</head>
				<figure rend="warn">
					<head><abbr rend="strong" type="acronym">F.B.I.</abbr> Warning</head>
					<p><graphic url="./badge.png" height="307px" width="255px" scale=".48"><desc>A circle with eight pointed spokes, reminiscent of a compass rose. Within the circle is the text <q type="written">Fengat Beureau of Investigations</q>.</desc></graphic>If you are reading this (which obviously you are), be warned: this book is officially outlawed by the government, and no matter which of the six colinies you are in you will be hunted down and killed. Do not try to flee, we have unimaginable knowledge and <emph>will</emph> find you<pc type="terminal">!</pc> This order complies to <abbr type="acronym">I.U.</abbr> order #1097</p>
					<closer>
						<signed>– <seg rend="cursiveonline">Joe Friscasa</seg></signed>
						Joe Friscasa, president
					</closer>
				</figure>
				<opener>
					<salute>
						<add place="margin">Dear Reader,</add>
					</salute>
				</opener>
				<p>Please do not panic; this note is no longer effective. Order #1097 was put out of action ten years ago. Just imagine my frustration, though, when I saw this posted on my books<pc type="terminal">!</pc> My own beureau, turned against me<pc type="terminal">!</pc> Of corse<note place="above" anchored="false"><abbr type="suspension">sp</abbr>?</note>, they couldn’t actually hurt you until you finished the first chapter, but still<pc type="terminal">!</pc> Who’s the agency named after anyway<pc type="terminal">?</pc> Joe Friscaso<pc type="terminal">?</pc> No<pc type="terminal">!</pc> It was named after me, and yet, it’s my book they’re placing <soCalled rend="oblique">read this and die</soCalled> stickers all over. All I was trying to do was release to the ignorant public the truth about Rylielectronics, but no, they won’t let me<pc type="terminal">!</pc> <q type="thought">Big deal,</q> I think, <q type="thought">it’s not like you’ll kill me, so I’ll publish it anyway<del>!</del><add place="inline">.</add></q><pc type="terminal"/> Then I saw those confounded stickers on my books<pc type="terminal">!</pc> Oh well, I guess it’s all over now, so until next time, farewell.</p>
				<closer>
					<signed>– Tyler Fengat</signed>
				</closer>
				<postscript>
					<label><abbr type="acronym">P.S.</abbr></label>
					<p>That unimaginable knowledge<add place="above">part</add> always<add place="above">makes me</add> laugh. All they’ve got is me, and it’s not like I’d tell them anything.</p>
				</postscript>
			</div>
		</front>
		<body xml:id="text">
			<head>Year 2109</head>
			<p>I don’t know what I was thinking when I joined the secret service. I guess I just wanted to have the experience. In any case, it was then when I found out about the Rylielectronics Project. The International Union had just passed a law stating all power plants and electrical companies were government owned. No one thought much of it, but I knew it’s true meaning, and I didn’t like it. The <abbr type="acronym">I.U.</abbr> had adjusted all the power lines to give power only to government products under the name of Rylielectronics, or products the government had approved of and put the power‐allowing chip in. The government said that this was to prevent anyone operating <soCalled>illegal and potentially dangerous objects.</soCalled><pc type="terminal"/> That may have been an additional reason, but the main reason was this: having a Rylielectronics chip means all your data is being broadcasted to Rylie, the main chip. Once completed,<note anchored="false" place="above"><abbr type="suspension">sp</abbr>?</note> Rylie and its bearer will have access to everybody’s files. Talk about violation of rights<pc type="terminal">!</pc> But the forming of the <abbr type="acronym">I.U.</abbr> violated all  other constitutions, and the <abbr type="acronym">I.U.</abbr> Constitution does not include the freedom of privacy. I was unsure of this, and so one afternoon asked.</p>
			<p><q type="spoken">Doesn’t Rylie violate some right or other?</q> I asked Commander Scrutin, a large brown‐haired man.</p>
			<p><q type="spoken">Nope. We made sure of that when we wrote the Constitution.</q> he replied. <q type="spoken">Now, it’s time for your cleaning.</q></p>
			<p>A cleaning is when all files relating to you are removed, and all who know you are sworn to secrecy. You replace your name with a letter and number until you retire. You effectively no longer exist. It was a ritual I, for one, did not want to do. <q type="spoken">Must I be cleaned?</q> I asked Scrutin.</p>
			<p><q type="spoken">If you want to live, yes.</q></p>
			<p>I was led down the hall to the cleaning room, where Captain Hoff was waiting to take charge of the cleaning.<add n="1" place="end">Hoff was a tall mean mannered man. Something about him made me nervous. Maybe it was the way he always frowned, or his large, scrutinizing<note anchored="false" place="above"><abbr type="suspension">sp</abbr>.</note> eyes.</add> <q type="spoken">Your parents and all other relatives or friends have been notified. All left to be removed is your name.</q><pc type="terminal"/> He typed a few figures into the computer. <q type="spoken">All files with your name have been destroyed. Your name exists only in memories. <del>You shall now be called R<seg rend="sub">41</seg>.</del><pc type="terminal"/> You may go.</q></p>
			<p>I left.</p>
		</body>
	</text>
</TEI>
