<?xml-model href="https://tei-c.org/release/xml/tei/custom/schema/relaxng/tei_lite.rng"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="https://go.KIBI.family/Tools/XSLT/KiT2X.xslt"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" href='data:text/css,
*.tei.TEI{ Background: Var(--PlainText) }
*.tei.teiHeader{ Background: Var(--Background) }
*.tei.text{ Margin: Auto; Padding: 2REM; Max-Inline-Size: 45REM; Color: Var(--PlainText); Background: Var(--Background); Font-Family: Sans-Serif; Line-Height: 1.2 }
*.tei.text *.tei.front,*.tei.text *.tei.body{ Margin: 0; Padding-Block: 1REM; Padding-Inline: 0 }
*.tei.text *.tei.front{ Border-Block-End: .1REM Solid }
*.tei.text *.tei.body::before{ Content: None }
*.tei.text *.tei.docTitle{ Margin: 0; Border: None }
*.tei.text *.tei.titlePart{ Margin: 0; Font-Family: Blackout Midnight, Serif; Font-Size: 4REM; Line-Height: 1; Text-Transform: None }
*.tei.text *.tei.titlePart[data--t-e-i_type=sub]{ Margin: 0; Font-Size: 1.5REM; Font-Weight: Bold }
*.tei.text *.tei.titlePart:Not([data--t-e-i_type=sub])~*.tei.docTitle[data--t-e-i_type=sub]{ Font-Size: 1.1REM }
*:root:root:root *.tei.text *.tei.div{ Margin: 0 }
*.tei.text>div>*>div>*.tei.div>div>*.tei.head{ Margin-Block: .83EM; Border-Block-End: .02REM Solid; Font-Family: League Gothic, Serif; Font-Size: 2REM; Text-Align: Start }
*.tei.text *.tei.head[data--t-e-i_n]::before{ Display: Inline; Font: Inherit; Text-Decoration: None; Content: Attr(data--t-e-i_n) " – " }
*.tei.text *.tei.p{ Margin-Block: .3REM 0; Text-Indent: 1.25REM }
*.tei.text *.tei.div[data--t-e-i_type=disclaimer] *.tei.p{ Font-Size: .8REM; Font-Family: League Gothic, Sans-Serif; Font-Style: Italic }
*.tei.text *.tei.ref{ Color: Var(--GreyText) }
*.tei.text *.tei.gap{ Font-Size: Inherit }
*.tei.text *.tei.q[data--t-e-i_type=spoken]::before{ Content: "“" }
*.tei.text *.tei.q[data--t-e-i_type=spoken]::after{ Content: "”" }
*.tei.text *.tei.q[data--t-e-i_type=spoken]+*.tei.seg.space{ Display: Inline }
*.tei.text *.tei.emph{ Font-Style: Italic }
*.tei.text *.tei.emph::before,*.tei.text *.tei.emph::after{ Content: None }
*.tei.mentioned.literal::before{ Content: "‹ " }
*.tei.mentioned.literal::after{ Content: " ›" }
'?>
<TEI xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0" xml:lang="en">
	<teiHeader>
		<fileDesc>
			<titleStmt>
				<title level="m">Tally Magiczl</title>
				<author><name>BJMNS</name></author>
			</titleStmt>
			<editionStmt>
				<edition>Version N, Draft 1<lb/><idno type="URI">tag:marrus.xyz,2016:bns::zl:N:1</idno></edition>
			</editionStmt>
			<publicationStmt>
				<publisher>KIBI Gô</publisher>
				<date when="2020">2020</date>
				<availability status="free">
					<licence target="https://creativecommons.org/publicdomain/zero/1.0/"><title level="m">CC0 1.0 Universal Public Domain Dedication</title></licence>
				</availability>
			</publicationStmt>
			<sourceDesc>
				<p>Born digital. Source is an HTML file.</p>
			</sourceDesc>
		</fileDesc>
		<encodingDesc>
			<editorialDecl>
				<p>In general, markup follows the HTML source. Hyphens have been normalized from hyphen‐dashes to <mentioned rend="literal"><pc>‐</pc></mentioned> and apostrophes have been normalized from straight single quotes to <mentioned rend="literal"><pc>’</pc></mentioned>. Prime and double‐prime have been normalized from straight quotes to <mentioned rend="literal"><pc>′</pc></mentioned> and <mentioned rend="literal"><pc>″</pc></mentioned>. No distinction between terminal and nonterminal punctuation is made.</p>
				<p>Author’s full name has been redacted from the copyright statement using <gi>gap</gi>.</p>
			</editorialDecl>
		</encodingDesc>
	</teiHeader>
	<text>
		<front>
			<docTitle>
				<titlePart type="sub">BJMNS Presents:</titlePart>
				<titlePart>Tally Magiczl</titlePart>
				<titlePart type="sub">A novel</titlePart>
			</docTitle>
			<div type="disclaimer">
				<head>Disclaimer</head>
				<p>This is a work of fiction<pc>.</pc> Any names, persons, events, or locales either are a product of the author’s mind or are used fictitiously<pc>.</pc> This work describes future events; note that such descriptions are used in a fictitious manner and are not meant as a prediction of actual future occurrences<pc>.</pc></p>
				<p>© 2013 <gap reason="editorial"><desc>author name</desc></gap><pc>.</pc> All rights reserved<pc>.</pc></p>
				<p><idno>BJMNS : 1.1.N.1</idno></p>
			</div>
		</front>
		<body xml:id="text">
			<div>
				<head n="I">[Chapter One]</head>
				 <p>Who was Tally Magiczl? For the most part, just your average kid: Dark brown hair, greenish eyes, about 5′10″ and 150 pounds<pc>.</pc> Eighteen years of age, and nearing graduation<pc>.</pc> Even the unusual things were pretty normal: A small scar on his face from when he was a kid, a pearl necklace worn under his shirt, a fondness for printed shirts that have gone out of fashion<pc>.</pc> To everyone around him, he was just another senior preparing to enter the <soCalled>real world</soCalled>, studying for the Final Exams, dreaming about university<pc>.</pc> But Tally had a secret<pc>.</pc></p>
				<p>Tally was a scientist<pc>.</pc></p>
				<p><q type="spoken">A scientist?</q> one might say<pc>.</pc> <q type="spoken">What good was a <emph>scientist</emph>?</q> Ever since the discovery of magic (or, some claimed, the re‐discovery) two centuries ago, there had been no need for <emph>sciences</emph><pc>.</pc> Every need was satisfied with a swish and a flick, and the funding for subjects of the scientific sort dried up long ago<pc>.</pc> <soCalled>Knowledge for knowledge’s sake</soCalled> was all fine and dandy, but someone has to pay the bills<pc>.</pc> When a rock could be turned into a strawberry with a the right words, what need was there for artificial flavors? Want a computer? Draw a keyboard on a piece of paper and the rest grew from there<pc>.</pc> There was no need to do the work oneself when the universe is so eager to please<pc>.</pc></p>
				<p>But here we have him: Tally Magiczl, scientist, working in the basement of his house, combining the elements in every which way, eyes glued to an old textbook that he had pulled from the twenty‐first century<pc>.</pc> His parents were at work, else he would be in his room studying: They didn’t approve of his hobby<pc>.</pc> <q type="spoken">You should be studying for the Exams,</q> they would say if they caught him<pc>.</pc> <q type="spoken">Quit filling your mind with inconsequential muck<pc>.</pc></q> But the fact of the matter was that Tally didn’t give a shit about the Final Exams, because he wasn’t a wizard<pc>.</pc></p>
				<p>Tally was a scientist.</p>
				<p>There were three degrees available to the aspiring magician, each requiring progressively more schooling and mastery of the art<pc>.</pc> In ascending order, they were: Beginner’s, Intermediate’s, and Wizard’s<pc>.</pc> The wizards were the ones who designed the spells that made the world turn (not quite literally), and they held the highest respect of the public<pc>.</pc> There were other fields as well, with the more traditional bachelor’s, master’s, and doctoral levels, in English and the like<pc>.</pc> But Tally cared for none of that: Nature didn’t speak English.</p>
				<p>The fact of the matter was that there was a lot about magic that didn’t make sense<pc>.</pc> Tally wasn’t the first to notice this; before their funding dried up, the physicists of old were equally mystified<pc>.</pc> But the higher‐ups decided that they rather preferred not knowing, and that was that<pc>.</pc> Science ceased to be profitable, and scientists learned to ignore the mysteries<pc>.</pc> Many became successful wizards: the two arts weren’t entirely non‐exclusive<pc>.</pc> But Tally couldn’t ignore the questions, he wanted answers, and he know only one way to get them: Experiment, and see what works<pc>.</pc></p>
				<p>It was strange, he thought, that no one cared why magic worked<pc>.</pc> It was the foundation of modern society; it was the solution to disease, poverty, war; and people didn’t care how or why it existed<pc>.</pc> Well, he cared<pc>.</pc></p>
				<p>Tally was a scientist<pc>.</pc></p>
			</div>
		</body>
	</text>
</TEI>
