<?xml-model href="https://tei-c.org/release/xml/tei/custom/schema/relaxng/tei_lite.rng"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="https://go.KIBI.family/Tools/XSLT/KiT2X.xslt"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" href='data:text/css,
*.tei.text *.tei.front,*.tei.text *.tei.body{ Margin: 0; Padding: 0; Hyphens: None }
*.tei.text *.tei.front>div{ Display: Grid; Grid-Template-Columns: Auto Max-Content }
*.tei.text *.tei.front *{ Grid-Column: 2 / Span 1; Font: Inherit; Margin: 0; Text-Align: Inherit; Text-Transform: None }
*.tei.text *.tei.front *.tei.docTitle{ Grid-Column: 1 / Span 2; Margin-Block: 4.5EM 3EM; Border: None; Text-Align: Center }
*.tei.text *.tei.body::before{ Content: None }
*.tei.text *.tei.trailer{ Margin-Block: 1.5EM; Margin-Inline: Auto; Inline-Size: 50%; Font-Weight: Inherit; Font-Variant-Caps: Inherit; Text-Align: Center }
*.tei.text *.tei.p{ Text-Align: Start; Text-Indent: 1.5EM }
*.tei.text *.tei.q::before,*.tei.titleStmt *.tei.q::before{ Content: "“" }
*.tei.text *.tei.q::after,*.tei.titleStmt *.tei.q::after{ Content: "”" }
*.tei.text *.tei.q+*.tei.seg.space,*.tei.titleStmt *.tei.q+*.tei.seg.space{ Display: Inline }
*.tei.text *.tei.title{ Text-Decoration: None }
*.tei.text *.tei.trailer *.tei.title{ Display: Block }
*.tei.text *.tei.seg.super{ Vertical-Align: Super }
*.tei.text *.tei.seg.sub{ Vertical-Align: Sub }
'?>
<TEI xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0" xml:lang="en">
	<teiHeader>
		<fileDesc>
			<titleStmt>
				<title level="m">Exasperated Wolf and the Boy who cried <q type="spoken">Wolf</q></title>
				<author><name>BJMNS</name><note>Not moniker recorded in source.</note></author>
			</titleStmt>
			<editionStmt>
				<edition><date when="2005-03-03">March 3, 2005</date><lb/><idno type="URI">tag:bjmns.tumblr.com,2013:bns::0:1:2:1</idno></edition>
			</editionStmt>
			<publicationStmt>
				<publisher>KIBI Gô</publisher>
				<date when="2020">2020</date>
				<availability status="free">
					<licence target="https://creativecommons.org/publicdomain/zero/1.0/"><title level="m">CC0 1.0 Universal Public Domain Dedication</title></licence>
				</availability>
				<ptr target="https://go.KIBI.family/Corpora/BJMNS/0/1/2/1/text.xml"/>
			</publicationStmt>
			<sourceDesc>
				<p>Source is a Rich Text Format file (original format unknown).</p>
			</sourceDesc>
		</fileDesc>
		<encodingDesc>
			<editorialDecl>
				<p>Quotes are marked up using TEI; no attempt to mark up names has been made, as they received no special treatment in the source.</p>
				<p>Author’s name and other potentially identifying information has been redacted using <gi>gap</gi>.</p>
				<p>Apostrophes have been normalized to <q type="literal"><pc>’</pc></q> and hyphens have been normalized to <q type="literal"><pc>‐</pc></q>.</p>
			</editorialDecl>
		</encodingDesc>
		<revisionDesc status="published">
			<change when="2020-08-04" status="published"><gi>revisionDesc</gi> added; minor changes to markup.</change>
			<change when="2020-07-26" status="published">Initial version based of a Rich Text Format source.</change>
		</revisionDesc>
	</teiHeader>
	<text>
		<front>
			<docAuthor><gap reason="editorial"><desc>author name</desc></gap></docAuthor>
			<docDate when="2005-03-05">March 3, 2005</docDate>
			<docTitle>
				<titlePart>Exasperated Wolf<lb/><seg rend="super">and</seg> <seg rend="sub">the</seg><lb/>Boy who cried <q type="spoken">Wolf</q></titlePart>
			</docTitle>
		</front>
		<body xml:id="text">
			<p>Exasperated Wolf hid in the cavity of a tree where it had rotted away. Birds had lived there, but they had migrated away to another area. He saw some sheep. Sheep are not poisonous, but are edible. They are also nourishing and good for you. He went to a remote and not occupied foundation (base) of a house. Nearby, a boy kept yelling, <q type="spoken">Wolf</q>, and a group of people would come, and when they saw there was no wolf, they began to have seemingly endless inquiries, like <q type="spoken">Why did you cry wolf?</q>  <q type="spoken">You were joking, weren’t you?</q> <q type="spoken">Why were you joking?</q> until no one could remember what the initial question was. Still, they persevered and didn’t stop until they got the full story out of him. They had so much persistence that no one could make them change their mind. Exasperated Wolf’s visibility was flawless and prefect, so he could see the whole thing. Exasperated Wolf used his ingenuity to come up with a plan. Since the boy was dependent and relied on others, once they were discouraged and wouldn’t come, he could make his move. He would kill a sheep and make it into a life like, realistic costume by installing a zipper. It might look rugged, course, or even like a three dimensional cartoon, but it would have to do. Just as singing lilting music might be a legacy passed from bird to bird, or that a good pianist makes melodious music, wolves always eat sheep. The more sheep you eat, the more tributes you get. The sheep Exasperated Wolf caught would have to not be miniature, but quite large. <q type="spoken">This will be an important milestone in history,</q> He thought.  <q type="spoken">The costume will be ornamental and decorative. The presentation I will make will be the best show ever<pc type="terminal">!</pc> If some one forges (makes) me a medal, I hope it is portable and moveable. I bet I will get a lot of recognition.</q></p>
			<p>While he was thinking this, the boy grabbed a pitchfork and sneaked up behind him. Then he scared Exasperated Wolf away.</p>
			<trailer>If you’re wondering why the story says that the wolf killed some sheep, find out in<pc rend="terminal">:</pc> <title>Mystified Tiger<lb/><seg rend="super">and</seg> <seg rend="sub">the</seg><lb/>Dog Who Cried <q type="spoken">Woof</q></title></trailer>
		</body>
	</text>
</TEI>
