<?xml-model href="https://tei-c.org/release/xml/tei/custom/schema/relaxng/tei_lite.rng"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="https://go.KIBI.family/Tools/XSLT/KiT2X.xslt"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" href='data:text/css,
*.tei.text *.tei.body{ Margin-Block: 1.5EM; Padding: 0; Hyphens: None }
*.tei.text *.tei.body *.tei.head{ Margin: 0; Font: Inherit; Text-Align: Start }
*.tei.text *.tei.p{ Text-Align: Start; Text-Indent: 1.5EM }
*.tei.text *.tei.q::before{ Content: "“" }
*.tei.text *.tei.q::after{ Content: "”" }
*.tei.text *.tei.q+*.tei.seg.space{ Display: Inline }
*.tei.text *.tei.div:Not(:First-Child){ Margin-Block-Start: 3EM }
*.tei.text *.tei.div:Not(:Last-Child){ Margin-Block-End: 3EM }
*.tei.text>div>*>div>*.tei.div:Not(:Last-Child){ Margin-Block-End: 4.5EM }
'?>
<TEI xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0" xml:lang="en">
	<teiHeader>
		<fileDesc>
			<titleStmt>
				<title level="m">Nat Gets Attacked by Ele the Alien Under the Sea</title>
				<author><name>BJMNS</name><note>Not recorded in source.</note></author>
			</titleStmt>
			<editionStmt>
				<edition><idno type="URI">tag:bjmns.tumblr.com,2013:bns::2:1:0:1</idno></edition>
			</editionStmt>
			<publicationStmt>
				<publisher>KIBI Gô</publisher>
				<date when="2020">2020</date>
				<availability status="free">
					<licence target="https://creativecommons.org/publicdomain/zero/1.0/"><title level="m">CC0 1.0 Universal Public Domain Dedication</title></licence>
				</availability>
				<ptr target="https://go.KIBI.family/Corpora/BJMNS/2/1/0/1/text.xml"/>
			</publicationStmt>
			<sourceDesc>
				<p>Born digital. Source is a plaintext file (original format unknown).</p>
			</sourceDesc>
		</fileDesc>
		<encodingDesc>
			<editorialDecl>
				<p>Quotes are marked up using TEI; no attempt to mark up names has been made, as they received no special treatment in the source.</p>
				<p>Source is broken up into multiple sections; these are encoded using <gi>div</gi>.</p>
				<p>Source designation of terminal punctuation (using two spaces) has been preserved via <gi>pc</gi> with a <val>terminal</val> <att>type</att>.</p>
				<p>The characters <q type="literal">π</q> and <q type="literal">ϊ</q>, as recorded here, are taken from a printed copy; in the source file used for this transcription, they were replaced with two NUL characters followed by either ETX or STX, respectively. It is likely that they are artefacts of a previous file format.</p>
			</editorialDecl>
		</encodingDesc>
		<revisionDesc status="published">
			<change when="2020-08-04" status="published"><gi>revisionDesc</gi> added; minor changes to markup.</change>
			<change when="2020-07-30" status="published">Initial version based off of a plaintext source.</change>
		</revisionDesc>
	</teiHeader>
	<text>
		<body xml:id="text">
			<head>Nat Gets Attacked by Ele the Alien Under the Sea</head>
			<div>
				<div>
					<p><q type="spoken">Dad can I jump off that cliff over there?</q><pc type="terminal"/> I begged.</p>
					<p><q type="spoken">Of course Nat,</q> my dad told me.</p>
					<p>Oh, let me introduce myself<pc type="terminal">.</pc> My name is Nat Shoemen<pc type="terminal">.</pc> I’m eight years old<pc type="terminal">.</pc> I am a boy and have dark brown eyes<pc>.</pc> My hair is pitch black and I have dark skin<pc type="terminal">.</pc> I weigh about 52.5 pounds and am four feet three inches tall<pc>.</pc> I love cliff diving into the ocean<pc type="terminal">.</pc> You cliff dive by going to the top of a cliff<pc type="terminal">.</pc> Then when you get to the top you dive into the water<pc>.</pc> Well, there are some things about me.</p>
					<p>Right now we are on vacation and at a cliff diving area<pc type="terminal">.</pc> The cliff diving area is over the Pacific Ocean<pc>.</pc> Now back to the story<pc type="terminal">.</pc> I went over to a cliff that was 300 feet high and I did a triple back flip off the edgeπ and into the ocean.</p>
					<p><q type="spoken">Sploosh!!!</q></p>
					<p xml:space="preserve">I landed in the murky water<pc type="terminal">.</pc> All of a sudden some seaweed wrapped around my leg<pc>.</pc> </p>
				</div>
				<div>
					<p xml:space="preserve">I looked down and stared at the evilest alien I had ever seen (I had only seen two before) yanking down on my leg<pc type="terminal">.</pc> She had pea green eyes, dark brown hair, freckles, and was three feet tall<pc>.</pc> She was wearing a green shirt, black pants and black boots<pc>.</pc> She pulled and tugged me further down under the ocean into a giant bubble<pc>.</pc> I finally let out my breath which I had been holding all of this time<pc>.</pc> I gazed around inside the bubble and was amazed at how elegant her home was<pc>.</pc> </p>
					<p><q type="spoken">Dad, I found a human</q> the alien told another alien, I think it was her father.</p>
					<p xml:space="preserve"><q type="spoken">Good work, Ele</q> the alien, who I think was the father, said<pc>.</pc><q type="spoken">Now we can start asking it questions.</q> </p>
					<p xml:space="preserve">I found out they were planning to invade Earth<pc type="terminal">.</pc> </p>
					<p><q type="spoken">I’m going to have to warn people</q> I said to myself<pc>.</pc> <q type="spoken">But, how?</q></p>
				</div>
				<div>
					<p>I knew the surface was too far under the ocean to ϊswim to the top<pc type="terminal">.</pc> I observed a dolphin through the wall of the bubble<pc>.</pc> <q type="spoken">If I could break through the wall of the bubble I could ride the dolphin to the surface.</q> I said to myself<pc>.</pc> I quickly exploded through the wall of the bubble and onto the dolphin as he raced by and he immediately swam to the surface near the shore<pc type="terminal">.</pc> I was out of breath, but I made it.</p>
				</div>
			</div>
			<div>
				<p xml:space="preserve">  Now, I needed to find a way to warn people of the planned invasion by aliens.</p>
				<p xml:space="preserve">I told my dad all that had just happened to me<pc>.</pc> </p>
				<p xml:space="preserve"><q type="spoken">Nat, there is no such thing as aliens</q> he explained to me<pc type="terminal">.</pc> </p>
				<p>I don’t know what happened to the aliens, but I am never going cliff diving again. I am sure of that.</p>
			</div>
		</body>
	</text>
</TEI>
